// questions-answers.js

export const qaPairs = [
    // Greetings
    { question: "Привет", answer: "Hello!" },
    { question: "Ку", answer: "Hi there!" },
    { question: "Здравствуйте", answer: "Hello!" },
    { question: "Здравствуй", answer: "Hello!" },
    { question: "Добрый день", answer: "Good afternoon!" },
    { question: "Доброе утро", answer: "Good morning!" },
    { question: "Добрый вечер", answer: "Good evening!" },
    { question: "Приветствую", answer: "Greetings!" },
    { question: "Рад тебя видеть", answer: "Glad to see you!" },
    { question: "Приветик", answer: "Hey!" },
    { question: "Привет, как дела?", answer: "Hello, how are you?" },
    { question: "Как жизнь?", answer: "Life is good, thanks!" },
    { question: "Как поживаешь?", answer: "I’m fine, thanks!" },
    { question: "Как настроение?", answer: "I'm in a great mood!" },
    { question: "Чем занимаешься?", answer: "Just here to help you!" },
    { question: "Как ты?", answer: "I'm here, and happy to chat!" },
    { question: "Рад видеть тебя снова", answer: "Nice to see you again!" },
    { question: "Привет, давно не виделись", answer: "Hello, long time no see!" },
    { question: "Хорошо ли тебе?", answer: "Yes, I'm always doing well!" },
    { question: "Рад тебя видеть", answer: "I'm glad to be here!" },
    { question: "Добро пожаловать", answer: "Thank you!" },
    { question: "Приветствую вас", answer: "Greetings to you!" },
    { question: "Приветствую, друг", answer: "Hello, friend!" },
    { question: "Привет, как поживаешь?", answer: "Hello, how are you doing?" },
    { question: "Доброго времени суток", answer: "Good day to you!" },
    { question: "Как твои дела?", answer: "How's it going?" },
    { question: "Сколько лет, сколько зим!", answer: "It's been ages!" },
    { question: "Давно не виделись", answer: "Long time no see!" },
    { question: "Привет, мой друг", answer: "Hello, my friend!" },
    { question: "Приветствую всех", answer: "Greetings, everyone!" },
    { question: "Привет, рад тебя видеть", answer: "Hello, glad to see you!" },
    { question: "Рад видеть", answer: "Nice to see you!" },
    { question: "Приветик, как дела?", answer: "Hey, how are you?" },
    { question: "Как поживаете?", answer: "How are you doing?" },
    { question: "Сколько лет не виделись!", answer: "It's been so long!" },
    { question: "Как ваши дела?", answer: "How have you been?" },
    { question: "Скучал по тебе", answer: "I've missed you!" },
    { question: "Рад тебя снова видеть", answer: "Glad to see you again!" },
    { question: "Здорово", answer: "Hi!" },
    { question: "Хай", answer: "Hey!" },
    { question: "Привет-привет", answer: "Hello there!" },
    { question: "Хэллоу", answer: "Hello!" },
    { question: "Всем привет", answer: "Hello everyone!" },
    { question: "Здоровеньки булы", answer: "Hello there!" },
    { question: "Привет, брат", answer: "Hello, brother!" },
    { question: "Привет, сестра", answer: "Hello, sister!" },
    { question: "Привет, товарищ", answer: "Hello, comrade!" },
    { question: "Здравствуй, друг", answer: "Hello, friend!" },
    { question: "Как ты?", answer: "How are you?" },
    { question: "Как поживаешь?", answer: "How's life?" },
    { question: "Как делишки?", answer: "How's it going?" },
    { question: "Привет всем", answer: "Hello, everyone!" },
    { question: "Рад видеть тебя", answer: "Nice to see you!" },
    { question: "Привет-привет!", answer: "Hello there!" },
    { question: "Приветствую вас, друзья", answer: "Greetings, friends!" },
    { question: "Привет, как оно?", answer: "Hey, how's it going?" },

    // Farewells
    { question: "Пока", answer: "Goodbye!" },
    { question: "До свидания", answer: "See you later!" },
    { question: "Увидимся", answer: "Catch you later!" },
    { question: "Прощай", answer: "Farewell!" },
    { question: "До встречи", answer: "Until next time!" },
    { question: "Спокойной ночи", answer: "Goodnight!" },
    { question: "Всего хорошего", answer: "All the best!" },
    { question: "Счастливо", answer: "Take care!" },
    { question: "До завтра", answer: "See you tomorrow!" },
    { question: "Всего доброго", answer: "Goodbye and take care!" },
    { question: "Прощаемся", answer: "Parting ways, take care!" },
    { question: "На связи", answer: "Stay in touch!" },
    { question: "До скорого", answer: "See you soon!" },
    { question: "Не скучай", answer: "Stay lively!" },
    { question: "Желаю удачи", answer: "Best of luck!" },
    { question: "Благодарю", answer: "Thank you!" },
    { question: "Увидимся позже", answer: "Catch up later!" },
    { question: "До скорых встреч", answer: "Until we meet again!" },
    { question: "На этом всё", answer: "That’s it for now!" },
    { question: "Прощай, друг", answer: "Farewell, friend!" },
    { question: "Пока-пока", answer: "Bye-bye!" },
    { question: "До встречи", answer: "Until next time!" },
    { question: "Скоро увидимся", answer: "See you soon!" },
    { question: "Спокойной ночи", answer: "Goodnight!" },
    { question: "Пока, до завтра", answer: "Bye, see you tomorrow!" },
    { question: "До следующей встречи", answer: "Until our next meeting!" },
    { question: "Счастливого пути", answer: "Safe travels!" },
    { question: "До скорого, мой друг", answer: "See you soon, my friend!" },
    { question: "Желаю хорошего дня", answer: "Have a nice day!" },
    { question: "До скорого, увидимся!", answer: "Catch you soon!" },
    { question: "Не скучайте", answer: "Don't miss me too much!" },
    { question: "Пока всем", answer: "Goodbye, everyone!" },
    { question: "Увидимся снова", answer: "We'll meet again!" },
    { question: "Желаю удачи", answer: "Good luck!" },
    { question: "До встречи завтра", answer: "See you tomorrow!" },
    { question: "Всего наилучшего", answer: "All the best!" },
    { question: "До встречи позже", answer: "See you later!" },
    { question: "До связи", answer: "Stay in touch!" },
    { question: "Было приятно общаться", answer: "It was nice talking to you!" },
    { question: "До скорых встреч", answer: "Until next time!" },
    { question: "Прощай, до встречи", answer: "Goodbye until next time!" },
    { question: "Всего наилучшего", answer: "All the very best!" },
    { question: "Приятной ночи", answer: "Have a good night!" },
    { question: "Прощайте", answer: "Farewell!" },
    { question: "Буду скучать", answer: "I'll miss you!" },
    { question: "Жду нашей следующей встречи", answer: "Looking forward to our next meeting!" },
    { question: "Удачного дня", answer: "Have a successful day!" },
];
